https://www.magaldi.com/en/privacy-policy/

Foundry
FOUNDRY (AL)
Foundry
Foundry (AL)
Foundry
FOUNDRY (AL)
Foundry
Foundry (AL)
PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy reports how www.magaldi.com website (hereafter: the "webite") processes users’ personal data.
This is a privacy policy made in compliance with art. 13 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679  of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (hereinafter: the "GDPR") and provided to all users who use and, more generally, interact with the services through the website by Magaldi Power SpA, based in Rome, at Piazza di Pietra, 26 (hereinafter: the "Controller" or “Magaldi”).
This privacy policy explains purposes and methods by which the Controller collects and processes your personal data, which categories of data are processed, which are the rights of data subjects and how they can be exercised.
The privacy policy is provided exclusively for this website and therefore Magaldi Power S.P.A. is not responsible for any other website to which the user may be redirected through the hyperlinks published on the website.
Users, using this website, accept this privacy policy and are therefore invited to review it before providing any personal information.
1. Categories of personal data
a. Navigation data
The computer systems and software procedures used to operate this website acquire, during their normal operation, some personal data whose transmission is implicit in the use of Internet communication protocols.
These information are not collected to be associated with identified data subjects, but for their nature they could, through processing and association with data held by third parties, allow users to be identified.
This category of data includes IP addresses or domain names of the devices used by users connecting to the website, the addresses in the Uniform Resource Identifier (URI) of the requested resources, the time of the request, the method used to submit the request to the server, the size of the file obtained in response, the numerical code reporting the status of the response given by the server (success, error, etc.) and other parameters relating to the operating system and user's device system.
These data are used for the sole purpose of obtaining anonymous statistical information on the use of the website and to check its correct functioning and are deleted immediately after processing. The data could be used to ascertain responsibility in case of hypothetical computer crimes against the website.
b. Data provided voluntarily by the user
Magaldi may acquire any personal data provided by the user through the website to access certain services (e.g. by filling out the contact form or signing up for the newsletter), or making requests by e-mail. By way of example, the website will acquire the name, surname, e-mail address and any other information which will be communicated directly by the data subject.
Through the website, the Controller will not acquire sensitive data or in any case belonging to the special categories referred to in art. 9 of GDPR or data relating to criminal convictions or offenses.
c. Data acquired in case of use of the services
The Controller may also acquire some personal data related to the registered user on the occasion of the use of the services offered by Magaldi Power S.p.A. through the website.
The personal data listed above will be processed by the Controller exclusively for the purposes and within the limits indicated in the following paragraph.
2. Purposes and legal basis of processing: provision of services requested
The data indicated in paragraph 1 lett. b) will be processed by the Controller to interact with the functions of the website and the use of services specifically related to it (for example, data communicated via the contact forms). The data will therefore be processed for the execution of requests made to the Controller.
The provision of such data is necessary. The provision of any data, not included in the contact forms, is not mandatory.
Subject to your consent, Magaldi may process your data for sending commercial communications through automated systems (e.g. e-mail, SMS, app notifications) and traditional communications systems (e.g. paper mail). For this purpose Magaldi shall process the data referred to in paragraph 1, lett. b) and c). The consent given is revocable at any time by writing to the Controller. Consent may also be revoked with reference to automated contact systems only.
3. Categories of subjects to whom personal data can be communicated and purposes of communication
The Controller may communicate, for the same purposes, some of your personal data also to third parties, who will process your personal data as Processors. The list of data processors may be requested from the Controller at any time.
The list of data processors may be requested from the Data Controller by writing to info@magaldi.com.
4. Period of data retention and duration of the processing
Your data will be kept for the entire duration of the contractual relationship with the Owner; following termination of the relationship, for any reason, the data will be kept for the strictly necessary period, exclusively for the needs of protection of the rights of the owner and for the fulfilment of legal obligations.
For marketing activities, the data will be stored and processed for the duration of the contractual relationship and for the next ten years, unless the previous revocation of consent by the data subject. In case of non-contractual relationship, the data will be processed until the time of revocation by the data subject.
5. Rights of the data subject
We inform you that, in compliance with current regulations, you have the following rights:
requesting and obtaining information about the existence of personal data in the availability of the Controller and access to such data;
for data processed with automated systems, requesting and transfering to another processor;
requesting and obtaining the modification and / or correction of your personal data if inaccurate or incomplete;
requesting and obtaining the cancellation - and / or the limitation of processing - of your personal data in the case of unnecessary data or information - or no longer necessary - for the above purposes, then after the retention period indicated in the paragraph above.
These requests may be sent to the Data Controller, by writing to Magaldi Power SpA, Piazza di Pietra, 26 - 00186 - Rome or to
group@magaldi.com
We also inform you that under the current regulations you can propose any complaints regarding the processing of your personal data to the Italian Data Protection Authority (Garante per la protezione dei dati personali).
Our website uses cookies to function correctly including third-party cookies.
If you are interested in getting some more detailed information about the processing of personal data or about the use of cookies and how to block all or part of them, visit the following link:
cookies.
Accept / Close
